Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Iron Mountain Indexed Materials, 1959-2005; undated; 4
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv_4--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-064)
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv_4--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-065)
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv_5--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-066)
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv_7--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-067)
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv_8--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-068)
  - 86AR_0182_TV_INT_50 Anniv--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-069)
  - 86AR_0183_TV_INT_50_Anniv_5--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 1986 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-222)
  - 86AR_0184_TV_INT_50_Anniv_7--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 1986 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-221)
  - 86AR_0185_TV_INT_50_Anniv_8--Consumers Union 50th anniversary dinner, 1986 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-212)
  - 86AR_0213_TV_PRO_Welcome--Welcome to Consumers Union, 1986 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-281)
  - 86AR_1213_TV_PRO_Welcome--Welcome to Consumers Union, 1986 Apr. 11 (Box 96, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-047)
  - 87AR_0030_TV_MED_CR_Univision--Consumer Reports on Univision, 1987 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-280)
  - 87AR_0030_TV_MED_CR_Univision--Consumer Reports on Univision, 1987 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-233)
  - 87AR_0030_TV_MED_CR_Univision--Consumer Reports on Univision, 1987 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0731)
  - 87AR_0044_TV_MED_Slice of Life--Consumer Reports "Slice of Life" :60 and :120, 1987 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-279)
  - 87AR_0044_TV_MED_Slice of Life-L66, 1987 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0313)
  - 88AR_0205_TV_PRO_Masters--Dexter Masters: Overview of Consumers Union; Conversations on Marketing, 1988 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-278)
  - 88AR_0214_TV_PRO_Test inform--Produced piece on what Consumers Union is about, 1988 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-277)
  - 88AR_1205_TV_PRO_Masters--Dexter Masters, 1988 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0317)
  - 88AR_1214_TV_PRO_Test Inform--Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 1988 Jan. 01-02 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0359)
  - 89AR_0011_TV_MED_GROH_60MIN--Ned Groh on CBS 60 Minutes, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-276)
  - 89AR_0012_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin, Today Show on toy safety, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-275)
  - 89AR_0012_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin, Today Show on toy safety, 1989 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0323)
  - 89AR_0148_TV_INT_Mason--Florence Mason interview, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-271)
  - 89AR_0148_TV_INT_Mason--Florence Mason interview, 1989 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0426)
  - 89AR_0148_TV_INT_Mason--Florence Mason interview, 1989 Mar. 13 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0425)
  - 89AR_0149_TV_INT_Building--New building start-up party, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-274)
  - 89AR_0149_TV_INT_Building--New building start-up party, 1989 Aug. 03 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0282)
  - 89AR_0150_TV_INT_Building--New building start-up party, 1989 Sept. 18 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0279)
  - 89AR_0151_TV_INT_Building--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-272)
  - 89AR_0151_TV_INT_Building--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1989 Oct. (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0314)
  - 89AR_0194_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions, Charlotte Baecher, 1989 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-273)
  - 90AR_0013_TV_MED_Letterman--David Letterman, Good Samaritan, 1990 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-270)
  - 90AR_0013_TV_MED_Letterman--David Letterman, Good Samaritan, 1990 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0337)
  - 90AR_0151_TV_INT_Building--New building, 1989 Sept. 18; 1990 Aug. 03 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0271)
  - 90AR_0151_TV_INT_Building--New building, 1990 Nov. 08 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0304)
  - 90AR_1052_TV_INT_Building--New building, 1990 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-269)
  - 91AR_0014_TV_MED_Schearer--Various clips from news programs, 1991 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-268)
  - 91AR_0014_TV_MED_Shearer--Clips from various news programs, 1991 May 16-17 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0250)
  - 91AR_0131_TV_INT_CU Annual--Consumers Union annual meeting, 1991 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-267)
  - 91AR_0131_TV_INT_CU Annual--Consumers Union annual meeting, 1991 Oct. 26 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0265)
  - 91AR_0153_TV_INT_Building Move--New building during move, 1991 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-266)
  - 91AR_0153_TV_INT_Building Move--New building during move, 1991 Feb. 16 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0293)
  - 91AR_0154_TV_INT_Dedication--Consumers Union dedication: Jim Guest, Rhoda Karpatkin, Betty Furness, 1991 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-265)
  - 91AR_0154_TV_INT_Dedication--Consumers Union new building dedication: Jim Guest, Rhoda Karpatkin, Betty Furness, 1991 May 30 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-178)
  - 91AR_0155_TV_INT_Dedication--Consumers Union dedication: Jim Guest, Rhoda Karpatkin, Betty Furness, 1991 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-264)
  - 91AR_0155_TV_INT_Dedication--Consumers Union new building dedication: Jim Guest, Rhoda Karpatkin, Betty Furness, 1991 May 30 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-180)
  - 92AR_0032_TV_MED_CU Testing--CBS This Morning on Consumers Union testing, 1992 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-204)
  - 92AR_0032_TV_MED_CU Testing--CBS This Morning on Consumers Union testing, 1992 Sept. 25 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0240)
  - 92AR_0036_TV_MED_Prime Time--Opening of Prime Time live with Consumer Reports mock cover, 1992 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-203)
  - 92AR_0036_TV_MED_Prime Time--Opening of Prime Time live with Consumer Reports mock cover, 1992 June 04 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0232)
  - 92AR_0038_TV_MED_Australia--Consumer Reports on Home Show Beyond 2000 (Australia), 1992 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-202)
  - 92AR_0038_TV_MED_Australia--Consumer Reports on Home Show Beyond 2000 (Australia), 1992 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0309)
  - 92AR_0145_TV_INT_CU_Editorial--Consumers Union Editorial Seminar, 1992 Apr. 27 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0288)
  - 92AR_0162_TV_INT_Peterson--Esther Peterson, 1992 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-201)
  - 92AR_0162_TV_INT_Peterson--Esther Peterson, 1992 Jan. 07 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0243)
  - 92AR_0211_TV_PRO_Looks at Kids--A Look at Kids as Consumers, 1992 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-200)
  - 92AR_1211_TV_PRO_Look at Kids--A Look at Kids as Consumers, 1992 Apr. 10 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-218)
  - 93AR_0015_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Who Shall Be Healed? Roundtable on health care with Rhoda Karpatkin, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-199)
  - 93AR_0015_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Who Shall Be Healed? Roundtable on health care with Rhoda Karpatkin, 1993 Jan. 27 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0424)
  - 93AR_0016_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin on Miller's Law (Court TV), 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-198)
  - 93AR_0016_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin on Miller's Law (Court TV), 1993 Dec. 22 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0332)
  - 93AR_0016_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin on Miller's Law (Court TV), 1993 Dec. 22 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0333)
  - 93AR_0028_TV_MED_CRTV Pilot--CRTV/CNBC pilot, composit open and stories, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-197)
  - 93AR_0028_TV_MED_CRTV Pilot--CRTV/CNBC pilot, composit open and stories, 1993 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0334)
  - 93AR_0132_TV_INT_BD_Addition--Annual Board Meeting and groundbreaking for addition to Consumers Union building, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-196)
  - 93AR_0132_TV_INT_BD_Addition--Annual Board Meeting and groundbreaking for addition to Consumers Union building, 1993 Oct. 16 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-217)
  - 93AR_0163_TV_INT_Interns--Luncheon for interns, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-195)
  - 93AR_0163_TV_INT_Interns--Luncheon for interns, 1993 Aug. 17 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0237)
  - 93AR_0164_TV_INT_Furness--Video tribute to Betty Furness, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-194)
  - 93AR_0164_TV_INT_Furness--Video tribute to Betty Furness, 1993 Oct. 16 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0226)
  - 93AR_0164_TV_INT_Furness--Video tribute to Betty Furness, 1993 Oct. 16 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0233)
  - 93AR_0188_TV_INT_Policy--Advocacy Offices seminar, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-193)
  - 93AR_0188_TV_INT_Policy--Advocacy Offices seminar, 1993 July 29 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0436)
  - 93AR_0188_TV_INT_Policy--Advocacy Offices seminar, 1993 July 29 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0439)
  - 93AR_0190_TV_INT_Guest--Jim Guest interview, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-192)
  - 93AR_0190_TV_INT_Guest--Jim Guest interview, 2002 Feb. 07 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0308)
  - 93AR_0215_TV_Test Inform Short--Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 1993 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-191)
  - 93AR_1215_TV_Pro_Test Inform--Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 1993 (Box 92, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0593)
  - 93AR_1215_TV_Pro_Test Inform--Welcome to Consumers Union 12:30 program, 1993 (Box 92, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-219)
  - 94AR_0017_TV_MED_Pres Clinton--President Clinton mentions Consumer Reports at White House Correspondents' Dinner (C-SPAN), 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-190)
  - 94AR_0017_TV_MED_Pres Clinton--President Clinton mentions Consumer Reports at White House Correspondents' Dinner (C-SPAN), 1994 Apr. 23 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0321)
  - 94AR_0018_TV_MED_Denver_Oprah--Eileen Denver on The Oprah Winfrey Show, topic of household hazards, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-189)
  - 94AR_0018_TV_MED_Denver_Oprah--Eileen Denver on The Oprah Winfrey Show, topic of household hazards, 1994 May 12 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0224)
  - 94AR_0018_TV_MED_Denver_Oprah--Eileen Denver on The Oprah Winfrey Show, topic of household hazards, 1994 May 12 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0238)
  - 94AR_0133_TV_INT_CU Annual--Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-188)
  - 94AR_0133_TV_INT_CU Annual--Consumers Union annual meeting, 1994 Oct. 15 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0228)
  - 94AR_0136_TV_INT_Karpatkin_AN--Annual Meeting, Rhoda Karpatking speech, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-187)
  - 94AR_0136_TV_INT_Karpatkin_AN--Consumers Union annual meeting, Rhoda Karpatkin speech, 2000 Oct. 21 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-174)
  - 94AR_0140_TV_INT_Staff Mtg--Consumers Union staff meeting, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-186)
  - 94AR_0140_TV_INT_Staff Mtg--Consumers Union staff meeting, 1994 May 23 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0286)
  - 94AR_0147_TV_INT_Bose--Brown Bag Lunch: Bose vs Consumers Union, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-185)
  - 94AR_0147_TV_INT_Bose--Brown Bag Lunch: Bose vs Consumers Union, 1994 Nov. 17 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0291)
  - 94AR_0165_TV_INT_Furness--Betty Furness memorial service, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-184)
  - 94AR_0165_TV_INT_Furness--Betty Furness memorial service, 1994 Apr. 18 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0297)
  - 94AR_0165_TV_INT_Furness--Betty Furness memorial service, 1994 Apr. 18 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0302)
  - 94AR_0165_TV_INT_PART 2--Old movie recorded off the air, 1994 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-183)
  - 95AR_0019_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin on CNBC Money Wheel, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-182)
  - 95AR_0019_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin on CNBC Money Wheel, 1995 Feb. 17 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0428)
  - 95AR_0033_TV_MED_Zillions--Zillions Our House (Lifetime) board games, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-181)
  - 95AR_0033_TV_MED_Zillions--Zillions Our House (Lifetime) board games, 1995 Mar. 07 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0354)
  - 95AR_0035_TV_MED_Buying Guide--Consumer Reports Buying Guide 11 News Weekend Report, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-180)
  - 95AR_0035_TV_MED_Buying Guide--Consumer Reports Buying Guide 11 News Weekend Report, 1995 Apr. 02 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0266)
  - 95AR_0040_TV_MED_Captive--15 media clips: 1) New building; 12) Captive Kids, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-179)
  - 95AR_0041_TV_MED_Captive--15 media clips: 1) New building; 12) Captive Kids, 1995 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0281)
  - 95AR_0141_TV_INT_Staff Mtg (Substituted 2/6/95 tape)--Consumers Union staff meeting, 1995 Feb. 06 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0227)
  - 95AR_0141_TV_INT_Staff Mtg--Consumers Union staff meeting, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-178)
  - 95AR_0141_TV_INT_Staff Mtg--Consumers Union staff meeting, 1995 May 10 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0301)
  - 95AR_0158_TV_INT_West Wing--West Wing ribbon cutting ceremony, 1995 Oct. 14 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0275)
  - 95AR_0158_TV_INT_West Wing--West Wing ribbon-cutting ceremony, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-177)
  - 95AR_0159_TV_INT_Dedication--Dedication ceremony of Yonkers building, 1995 July 28 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0272)
  - 95AR_0159_TV_INT_Dedication--West Wing ribbon-cutting ceremony and dedication, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-176)
  - 95AR_0166_TV_INT_Safety Seats--Consumer Reports b-roll child safety seats crash tests, 1995 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-175)
  - 95AR_0166_TV_INT_Safety Seats--Consumer Reports b-roll: child safety seat tests, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-175)
  - 95AR_0167_TV_INT_Berliner OPI--David Berliner, Office of Public Information presentation, "Through the Years", 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-173)
  - 95AR_0167_TV_INT_Berliner OPI--David Berliner, Office of Public Information presentation, "Through the Years", 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-174)
  - 95AR_0167_TV_INT_Berliner OPI--Office of Public Information presentation, David Berliner "Through the Years", 1996 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0225)
  - 95AR_0208_TV_PRO_Captive Kids--WABC Captive Kids, 1995 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-172)
  - 95AR_1208_TV_PRO_Captive Kids--WABC Captive Kids, 1995 Apr. 18 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-183)
  - 95AR_1208_TV_PRO_Captive Kids--WABC Captive Kids, 1995 Apr. 18 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-184)
  - 96AR_0020_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Brazil TV Globo interview with Rhoda Karpatkin, 1996 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-171)
  - 96AR_0020_TV_MED_Karpatkin--Brazil TV Globo interview with Rhoda Karpatkin, 1996 Aug. 05 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0336)
  - 96AR_0027_TV_MED_Prime Time--Prime Time Live episode, 1996 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-170)
  - 96AR_0027_TV_MED_PrimeTime--Prime Time Live episode, 1996 May 22 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0324)
  - 96AR_0142_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1996 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-169)
  - 96AR_0142_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1996 May 15 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0440)
  - 96AR_0142_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1996 May 15 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0441)
  - 97AR_0021_TV_MED_MAYS_GMA--Good Morning America episode, Don Mays on exercise and weight loss, 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-168)
  - 97AR_0021_TV_MED_MAYS_GMA--Good Morning America segment with Don Mays on exercise and diet, 1997 Sept. 23 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0318)
  - 97AR_0022_TV_MED_Reynolds--Paul Reynolds on The O'Reilly Report, "Selling It on TV", 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-167)
  - 97AR_0022_TV_MED_Reynolds--The O'Reilly Report segment with Paul Reynolds, Selling It on TV, 1997 Dec. 02 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0326)
  - 97AR_0134_TV_INT_CU Annual--Consumers Union annual meeting, 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-166)
  - 97AR_0134_TV_INT_CU Annual--Consumers Union annual meeting, 1997 Oct. 25 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0262)
  - 97AR_0143_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-165)
  - 97AR_0143_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1997 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0310)
  - 97AR_0146_TV_INT_CU Seminar--Consumers Union Seminar starting with PBS "In the Mix", 1997 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0303)
  - 97AR_0146_TV_INT_CU Seminar--Consumers Union Seminar, Starting with PBS "In the Mix", 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-164)
  - 97AR_0146-2_TV_INT_CU Seminar--Consumers Union Seminar, Starting with PBS "In the Mix", 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-163)
  - 97AR_0168_TV_INT_Knoll tribute--Retirement tribute to Bob Knoll, 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-162)
  - 97AR_0168_TV_INT_Knoll tribute--Retirement tribute to Bob Knoll, 1997 May 27 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0245)
  - 97AR_0169_TV_INT_CPSC--Consumer Product Safety Commission Chairman Ann Brown, 1997 June 02 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0248)
  - 97AR_0169_TV_INT_CPSC--Consumer Product Safety Commission Chairman Ann Brown, 1997 June 02 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0267)
  - 97AR_0169_TV_INT_CPSC--Consumer Products Safety Commission Chairman Ann Brown, 1997 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-161)
  - 98AR_0024_TV_MED_Squares--Hollywood Squares segment featuring Consumer Reports, 1998 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-160)
  - 98AR_0024_TV_MED_Squares--Hollywood Squares segment featuring Consumer Reports, 1998 Oct. 28 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0427)
  - 98AR_1194_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions, 1989 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0249)
  - 99AR_0023_TV_MED_Pittle_Auto--NBC Nightly News with Tom Brokaw: Small car safety featuring David Pittle, 1998 Apr. 27 (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0430)
  - 99AR_0029_TV_MED_CR Testing--CBS 60 Minutes segment on Consumer Reports testing, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-158)
  - 99AR_0029_TV_MED_CR Testing--CBS 60 Minutes segment on Consumer Reports testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0347)
  - 99AR_0029_TV_MED_CR Testing--CBS 60 Minutes segment on Consumer Reports testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0348)
  - 99AR_0029_TV_MED_CR Testing--CBS 60 Minutes segment on Consumer Reports testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0349)
  - 99AR_0029_TV_MED_Pittle_Auto--NBC Nightly News with Tom Brokaw: Small car safety featuring David Pittle, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-159)
  - 99AR_0031_TV_MED_CR Operates--ABC World News Tonight segment on how Consumer Reports operates, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-157)
  - 99AR_0031_TV_MED_CR Operates--ABC World News Tonight segment on how Consumer Reports operates, 1999 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0355)
  - 99AR_0144_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-156)
  - 99AR_0144_TV_INT_Town--Consumers Union Town Meeting, 1999 Nov. 11 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0311)
  - 99AR_0160_TV_INT_Yonkers bldg. B--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-155)
  - 99AR_0160_TV_INT_Yonkers bldg.--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1991 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-185)
  - 99AR_0160_TV_INT_Yonkers bldg.--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-154)
  - 99AR_0160_TV_INT_Yonkers bldg.--Consumers Union Yonkers building, 1999 June 03 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0241)
  - 99AR_0170_TV_INT_Labs--Some labs at Consumers Union, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-153)
  - 99AR_0170_TV_INT_Labs--Some labs at Consumers Union, 1999 June (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-179)
  - 99AR_0186_TV_INT_Champion1--Satellite interviews with David Champion on Auto Issue 4/99, History #1, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-152)
  - 99AR_0186_TV_INT_Champion1--Satellite interviews with David Champion on Auto Issue 4/99, History #1, 1999 Apr. 06 (Box 96, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-116)
  - 99AR_0187_TV_INT_Champion2--Satellite interviews with David Champion on Auto Issue 4/99, History #2, 1999 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-151)
  - 99AR_0187_TV_INT_Champion2--Satellite interviews with David Champion on Auto Issue 4/99, History #2, 1999 Apr. 06 (Box 96, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-117)
  - XXAR_0019_AU_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-226)
  - XXAR_0019_AU_Karpatkin--Rhoda Karpatkin, Undated (Box 94, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-206)
  - XXAR_0020_AU_Masters--Dexter Masters, Undated (Box 94, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-195)
  - XXAR_0021_AU_Warne Money--Colston Warne, 1971 (Box 94, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-197)
  - XXAR_0021_AU_Warne_Money--Colston Warne, 1971 (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-225)
  - XXAR_0025_TV_MED_Testers--Testing the Testers with Paula Lynne, WCVB-TV News, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-224)
  - XXAR_0025_TV_MED_Testers--Testing the Testers with Paula Lynne, WCVB-TV News, Undated (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-225)
  - XXAR_0026_TV_MED_Zillions--Consumer Reports Magazine: Knoll, Daviet, Zillions, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-223)
  - XXAR_0026_TV_MED_Zillions--Consumer Reports Magazine: Knoll, Daviet, Zillions, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0315)
  - XXAR_0034_TV_MED_Advocacy--Gene Kimmelman on NewsHour, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-222)
  - XXAR_0034_TV_MED_Advocacy--Gene Kimmelman on NewsHour, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0316)
  - XXAR_0037_TV_MED_Murphy Brown--Consumer Reports on Murphy Brown television show, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-221)
  - XXAR_0037_TV_MED_Murphy Brown--Consumer Reports on Murphy Brown television show, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0276)
  - XXAR_0045_TV_MED_60 Minutes--World News Tonight, 60 Minutes: Asa Arons, Laurie Berger, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0287)
  - XXAR_0046_TV_MED_AUTO--How We Test at ATD, NBC Today Show about the 4/01 Auto Issue, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-212)
  - XXAR_0046_TV_MED_AUTO--How We Test at ATD, NBC Today Show about the 4/01 Auto Issue, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0263)
  - XXAR_0047_TV_INT_Siegel1--Sylvia Siegel video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-220)
  - XXAR_0047_TV_INT_Siegel1--Sylvia Siegel video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0251)
  - XXAR_0048_TV_INT_Siegel2--Sylvia Siegel video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-219)
  - XXAR_0048_TV_INT_Siegel2--Sylvia Siegel video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0229)
  - XXAR_0049_TV_INT_Silbergeld1--Mark Silbergeld video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-218)
  - XXAR_0049_TV_INT_Silbergeld1--Mark Silbergeld video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0255)
  - XXAR_0050_TV_INT_Silbergeld2--Mark Silbergeld video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-211)
  - XXAR_0050_TV_INT_Silbergeld2--Mark Silbergeld video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0239)
  - XXAR_0051_TV_INT_Shepard--Gary Shepard on consumer rights, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-217)
  - XXAR_0051_TV_INT_Shepard--Gary Shepard on consumer rights, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0285)
  - XXAR_0052_TV_INT_Shapiro1--Esther K. Shapiro video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-216)
  - XXAR_0052_TV_INT_Shapiro1--Esther K. Shapiro video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0230)